siam-legal.com 2019-05-15

# Privacy Policy | Siam Legal International

Www.siam-legal.com is a website which deals with commercial services, legal disputes, visa applications, and other legal services in Thailand. This Privacy Policy is indicative of our commitment to secure the privacy of our visitors. It outlines how we protect the information given to us. It describes how we collect and use such information to improve the Service. By using the Service, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. Unless otherwise defined in this Privacy Policy, terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our [Terms and Conditions](https://www.siam-legal.com/terms_of_use.php)

### Definitions

**Service**  
Service is the https://www.siam-legal.com website operated by Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd.

**Personal Data**  
Personal Data means data about an individual who can be identified from those data (or from those and other information either in our possession or likely to come into our possession).

**Usage Data**  
Usage Data is data collected automatically either generated by the use of the Service or from the Service infrastructure itself (for example, the duration of a page visit).

**Cookies**  
Cookies are small pieces of data stored on your device (computer, tablet or mobile device).

**Data Controller**  
Data Controller means the natural or legal person who (either alone or jointly or in common with other persons) determines the purposes for which and the manner in which any personal information are, or are to be, processed. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, we are a Data Controller of your Personal Data.

**Data Processors (or Service Providers)**  
Data Processor (or Service Provider) means any natural or legal person who processes the data on behalf of the Data Controller. We may use the services of various Service Providers in order to process your data more effectively.

**Data Subject (or User)**  
Data Subject is any living individual who is using our Service and is the subject of Personal Data.

### Collection and Use of Information

Our Privacy Policy covers all online information consisting of personal identifiable or non-personal identifiable information shared with us while visiting our website. It does not cover offline information. We collect these information for various purposes to provide and improve our Service to you.

The personal information supplied to the website is used to provide services, carry out the transactions expected of us, process requests and notify clients of any material change to this Privacy Policy.

The non-personally identifiable information, on the other hand, shall be used to manage the website. It may be used to analyze data for easy navigation and access on the website.

Hence, the use of the website signifies your agreement with all the terms of the Privacy Policy.

Should you not want us to use your personal identification, do not submit any information to the website or to any of our lawyers.

### Types of Data Collected

**Personal Data**  
While using our Service, we may ask you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Data”). Personally identifiable information may include, but is not limited to:

  * First and last name
  * Email address
  * Contact number
  * Nationality
  * Location data
  * Cookies and Usage Data

We may use your Personal Data to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send or by contacting us.

**Usage Data**  
We may also collect information how the Service is accessed and used ("Usage Data"). This Usage Data may include information such as your computer’s Internet Protocol address (e.g. IP address), browser type, browser version, the pages of our Service that you visit, the time and date of your visit, the time spent on those pages, unique device identifiers and other diagnostic data.

**Location Data**  
We may use and store information about your location if you give us permission to do so ("Location Data"). We use this data to provide features of our Service, to improve and customize our Service and to know where to concentrate our marketing efforts. You can enable or disable location services when you use our Service at any time, through your device settings.

**Tracking and Cookies Data**  
Cookies are files with small amount of data which may include an anonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Tracking technologies also used are beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Service.

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track the activity on our Service and hold certain information.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies, you may not be able to use some portions of the Service.

Examples of Cookies we use:  

  * _Session Cookies._ We use Session Cookies to operate our Service.
  * _Preference Cookies._ We use Preference Cookies to remember your preferences and various settings.
  * _Security Cookies._ We use Security Cookies for security purposes.

### Usage Data

Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd. uses the collected data for various purposes:

  * To provide and maintain our Service
  * To notify you about changes to our Service
  * To provide customer support
  * To gather analysis or valuable information so that we can improve our Service and marketing
  * To monitor the usage of our Service
  * To detect, prevent and address technical issues
  * To provide you with news, special offers and general information about other goods, services and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or enquired about unless you have opted not to receive such information

### Legal Basis for Processing Personal Data Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are from the European Economic Area (EEA), Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd. legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Data we collect and the specific context in which we collect it.

Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd. may process your Personal Data because:

  * We need to perform a contract with you
  * You have given us permission to do so
  * The processing is in our legitimate interests and it’s not overridden by your rights
  * To comply with the law

### Data Retention

Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd. will retain your Personal Data only for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your Personal Data to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations (for example, if we are required to retain your data to comply with applicable laws), resolve disputes, and enforce our legal agreements and policies.

Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd. will also retain Usage Data for internal analysis purposes. Usage Data is generally retained for a shorter period of time, except when this data is used to strengthen the security or to improve the functionality of our Service, or we are legally obligated to retain this data for longer time periods.

### Transfer of Data

Your information, including Personal Data, may be transferred to — and maintained on — computers located outside of your state, province, country or other governmental jurisdiction where the data protection laws may differ than those from your jurisdiction.

If you are located outside Thailand and choose to provide information to us, please note that we transfer the data, including Personal Data, to Thailand and process it there.

Your consent to this Privacy Policy followed by your submission of such information represents your agreement to that transfer.

Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd. will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy and no transfer of your Personal Data will take place to an organization or a country unless there are adequate controls in place including the security of your data and other personal information.

### Disclosure of Data

**Business Transaction**  
If Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd. is involved in a merger, acquisition or asset sale, your Personal Data may be transferred. We will provide notice before your Personal Data is transferred and becomes subject to a different Privacy Policy.

**Disclosure for Law Enforcement**  
Under certain circumstances, Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd. may be required to disclose your Personal Data if required to do so by law or in response to valid requests by public authorities (e.g. a court or a government agency).

**Legal Requirements**  
Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd. may disclose your Personal Data in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to:

  * To comply with a legal obligation
  * To protect and defend the rights or property of Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd.
  * To prevent or investigate possible wrongdoing in connection with the Service
  * To protect the personal safety of users of the Service or the public
  * To protect against legal liability

### Security of Data

The security of your data is important to us, but remember that no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. While we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Data, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### "Do Not Track" Signals Under California Online Privacy Protection Act (CalOPPA)

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT"). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked.

You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

### Your Data Protection Rights Under General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR)

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd. aims to take reasonable steps to allow you to correct, amend, delete, or limit the use of your Personal Data.

If you wish to be informed what Personal Data we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

  * The right to access, update or to delete the information we have on you. Whenever made possible, you can request deletion of your Personal Data by [contacting us](https://www.siam-legal.com/contactus.php).
  * The right of rectification. You have the right to have your information rectified if that information is inaccurate or incomplete.
  * The right to object. You have the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data.
  * The right of restriction. You have the right to request that we restrict the processing of your personal information.
  * The right to data portability. You have the right to be provided with a copy of the information we have on you in a structured, machine-readable and commonly used format.
  * The right to withdraw consent. You also have the right to withdraw your consent at any time where Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd. relied on your consent to process your personal information.

Please note that we may ask you to verify your identity before responding to such requests.

You have the right to complain to a Data Protection Authority about our collection and use of your Personal Data. For more information, please contact your local data protection authority in the European Economic Area (EEA).

### Service Providers

We may employ third party companies and individuals to facilitate our Service ("Service Providers"), to provide the Service on our behalf, to perform Service-related services or to assist us in analyzing how our Service is used.

These third parties have access to your Personal Data only to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for any other purpose.

**Analytics**  
We may use third-party Service Providers to monitor and analyze the use of our Service. 

  * **Google Analytics**  
Google Analytics is a web analytics service offered by Google that tracks and reports website traffic. Google uses the data collected to track and monitor the use of our Service. This data is shared with other Google services. Google may use the collected data to contextualize and personalize the ads of its own advertising network.

You can opt-out of having made your activity on the Service available to Google Analytics by installing the Google Analytics opt-out browser add-on. The add-on prevents the Google Analytics JavaScript (ga.js, analytics.js, and dc.js) from sharing information with Google Analytics about visits activity.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

**Behavioral Remarketing**  
Siam Legal (Thailand) Co., Ltd. uses remarketing services to advertise on third party websites to you after you visited our Service. We and our third-party vendors use cookies to inform, optimize and serve ads based on your past visits to our Service.

  * **Google AdWords**  
Google AdWords remarketing service is provided by Google Inc.

You can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize the Google Display Network ads by visiting the Google Ads Settings page: <http://www.google.com/settings/ads>

Google also recommends installing the Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on – <https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout> – for your web browser. Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on provides visitors with the ability to prevent their data from being collected and used by Google Analytics.

For more information on the privacy practices of Google, please visit the Google Privacy & Terms web page: <https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en>

### Information Collected by Third Parties

As our website is linked to other websites, this Privacy Policy does not apply to other linked websites. It is advised that you consult their own privacy policy as they have different policies regarding the use of their respective sites. Consequently, we have no control over the information submitted by or in possession of third parties.

### Children’s Privacy

Our Service does not address anyone under the age of 18 ("Children").

We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from anyone under the age of 18. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with Personal Data, please contact us. If we become aware that we have collected Personal Data from children without verification of parental consent, we take steps to remove that information from our servers.

### Privacy Notice

This website reserves the right to amend or supplement the contents and/or information without prior notice. Any changes made to the website shall become effective on the date of posting. The use of the website after such posting constitutes consent thereto. Thus, it is advised to periodically review the Privacy Policy of the website before using it.

In case of revision and information is required, a notice may be sent informing you of the reason for the change, of the need for the information we sought from you, and the choices granted to you regarding its use.

### Governing Law

The laws of Thailand govern this Privacy Policy without regard to its conflict of law provision.

If you have any query regarding our Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
